<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on NoSlackDev</title>
    <link>https://noslackdev.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on NoSlackDev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2019 Stephen Stanton</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2019 10:53:26 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://noslackdev.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UpdatedApproach</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/posts/updatedapproach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 05:05:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/posts/updatedapproach/</guid>
      <description>Hot off the heels of a much needed vacation, and also of a big gap in my studies, its time to re-commit and update my approach to this endeavor. I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on completing one chapter/lecture/problem set or other &amp;ldquo;unit&amp;rdquo; of work per day and to get either a twitter post or a blog post done each day as well. Posts to twitter will be &amp;ldquo;accountability posts&amp;rdquo;, which are done as a way of holding myself accountable by feeling some pressure to check-in daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS50 Week 1</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/posts/cs50-week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 08:45:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/posts/cs50-week-1/</guid>
      <description>I finished Week 1 the week before last. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t much of a struggle as I&amp;rsquo;ve been through this week before. I finished the Hello, Mario (More), and Credit in pretty quick succession.
The Credit assignment was fun because it has some overlap in what I do in my day job. We work closely with payment gateways and credit card processing on some of our projects, so I ended up in familiar territory with this assignment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS50 Week 0</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/posts/cs50-week-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 06:47:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/posts/cs50-week-0/</guid>
      <description>While on the road for work last week, I watched the Week 0 lecture and completed the problem set. This was probably the 3rd or 4th time I&amp;rsquo;ve watched this lecture, since I&amp;rsquo;ve started and not completed CS50 several times. CS50 re-records the lecture each year for the live class at Harvard, and online students like myself get the benefit of updated materials. The content is pretty consistent from year to year, but the execution continues to improve (impressive, considering how good it is to begin with).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Begin CS50</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/posts/begin-cs50/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 21:55:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/posts/begin-cs50/</guid>
      <description>The journey begins with CS50.
I&amp;rsquo;ve started this course a few times over the years, and only made it through the first two or three problem sets before my attention moved elsewhere. The experience I have had with it so far has been very positive. The content is very well produced and is refreshed often if I remember correctly. The instructor, David Malan, is very engaging and a pleasure to learn from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/meta/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:24:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/meta/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Stephen. Welcome to NoSlackDev.
This first post is also represented in the About section.
The idea behind this blog is still forming, but instead of trying to have a fully fleshed out idea before starting it, I thought it wise to just start&amp;hellip; and see where it goes.
This is a blog about learning and improving in general, with a particular focus around software development. I seek to guide myself through a growing curriculum of classes, books, projects, and other activities to improve myself in many ways: as a technologist, a developer, a problem solver, a thinker, a builder, a consultant, and in a variety of other skills and interests that I may write about here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>