<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meta on NoSlackDev</title>
    <link>https://noslackdev.com/categories/meta/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meta on NoSlackDev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2019 Stephen Stanton</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 05:05:30 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://noslackdev.com/categories/meta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>UpdatedApproach</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/posts/updatedapproach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 05:05:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/posts/updatedapproach/</guid>
      <description>Hot off the heels of a much needed vacation, and also of a big gap in my studies, its time to re-commit and update my approach to this endeavor. I&amp;rsquo;m going to focus on completing one chapter/lecture/problem set or other &amp;ldquo;unit&amp;rdquo; of work per day and to get either a twitter post or a blog post done each day as well. Posts to twitter will be &amp;ldquo;accountability posts&amp;rdquo;, which are done as a way of holding myself accountable by feeling some pressure to check-in daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://noslackdev.com/meta/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Mar 2019 10:24:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://noslackdev.com/meta/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Stephen. Welcome to NoSlackDev.
This first post is also represented in the About section.
The idea behind this blog is still forming, but instead of trying to have a fully fleshed out idea before starting it, I thought it wise to just start&amp;hellip; and see where it goes.
This is a blog about learning and improving in general, with a particular focus around software development. I seek to guide myself through a growing curriculum of classes, books, projects, and other activities to improve myself in many ways: as a technologist, a developer, a problem solver, a thinker, a builder, a consultant, and in a variety of other skills and interests that I may write about here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>